Difficulty: Easy

The Goal:
Given an array of integers nums and an integer target, return the indices of the two numbers such that they add up to target. 

Constraints:
Each input has exactly one solution.
You may not use the same element twice.
You can return the answer in any order. 

Example:
Input: nums = [2, 7, 11, 15], target = 9
Output: [0, 1] (Because nums[0] + nums[1] == 9)

Bonus points:
Can you solve it with a time complexity better than O of n sqr