Longest Substring Without Repeating Characters

Difficulty: Medium (but very doable with your Dictionary experience!)

The Goal:
Given a string s, find the length of the longest substring without repeating characters.

Example:
Input: s = "abcabcbb"
Output: 3 (The longest substring is "abc")

Input: s = "bbbbb"
Output: 1 (The longest substring is "b")

Input: s = "pwwkew"
Output: 3 (The longest substring is "wke". Note that "pwke" is a subsequence, but not a substring.)

